testden.com 2017-03-13

# TestDEN Privacy Policy

TestDEN is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Website, so we want you to know what information we collect, how we use that information, and how you can update it. 

**Information That We Collect**  
We collect various types of information from our visitors so we can adjust the website to meet our users' needs and expectations. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies. Other information is collected when you register for any TestDEN online services or when you request information from one of our partners. 

**Information Collected Automatically**  
The types of information your browser or Internet session automatically sends us each time you visit one of our sites, which we automatically collect, includes: 

  * Your browser.
  * Your computer's operating system.
  * Your navigation path, i.e., the URLs of where you come to our site from, which of our pages you visit, and where you go as you leave.
  * Your IP address.

This and other information lets us see how users are finding TestDEN, and it tells us which pages are visited the most often so we can make our website more useful. 

**Information You Provide to TestDEN**  
In addition to the information automatically collected by your browser, we also collect information that you provide to us when you register for a TestDEN online service or course, or request information about a particular school or educational program. Our website provides users with online practice tests, test preparation courses, and accent training materials. These online services require users to provide TestDEN with contact information (name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number). We collect this information in order to validate user purchases and process payment for TestDEN online services. 

Our website also provides users with information about various education opportunities and to request information from schools. These information request forms require users to provide TestDEN with contact information (name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and other details) as well as information about their interest in one of our educational partners (universities, colleges, and language schools). We collect this information that you provide, and forward to our educational partners that you requested information from. 

**How We Use This Information**  
We use the information we automatically collect to help us better plan our website to meet your Internet needs. Information you provide to us is used for marketing purposes, and may result in follow-up communications. In addition, from time to time, we may share personally identifiable information (such as e-mail addresses) about our customer base with carefully selected third parties, so they can offer goods and services that we believe may be of interest to our customers. All third parties are bound by the federal CAN-SPAM Act and required to follow all consumer opt out rules and regulations. 

**Your Rights and Our Obligations**  
TestDEN respects the privacy of users visiting our site and will abide by all applicable laws concerning the release of personal information. We may use certain directory information that we have collected to send you information about products and services, or updates and other information we think may be of interest to you. We may share this information with our educational partners to bring similar information to your attention. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. Please contact us to request your name and address be removed from our lists. If you do not want to receive our e-mail marketing, please submit a request to have your e-mail address removed by emailing: comment@testden.com. 

**Third Party Cookies**  
TestDEN.com uses the following third-party cookies: 

_Google Analytics_ \- This cookie allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, source and time spent on website. The information is depersonalised and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. Using Google Analytics, we can see what content is useful and popular on our website which helps us to provide better content and tools for our visitors. _Google Adwords_ \- Using Google AdWords code we are able to see which pages led to TestDEN.com test prep service sign-ups. This allows us to make better use of our online advertising budget. _Remarketing Advertising We Use_ \- We use Google Remarketing tags to advertise trigger across the Internet. Google remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the TriggerApp website you have viewed by placing a pixel tag on your machine. THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANYWAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER. The cookie is used to say "This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page." Google AdWords Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you. _Social Sharing Cookies_ \- TestDEN.com uses social sharing buttons for services including, but not limited to, Twitter, Google+ and Facebook. These allow you to share pages with your friends via those networks. While you will be asked to login to use these services, this process is handled directly with the social sharing providers and their databases and servers. These sites may also monitor your usage of these buttons, through the use of external tracking codes that are required to run the buttons on TestDEN.com. _Email Tracking Codes_ \- TestDEN.com email communications with you may include tracking codes that help us understand who, as well as how many people have opened or clicked on each email. This data helps us to create better emails in the future, and provide you with a better service. This data is stored on the servers of our email partners and covered under their security measures. 

**Legal Protections and Law Enforcement**  
We may disclose information about our users, including your personal information, in the event we are required to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or other valid law enforcement measures; to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the website and applicable laws; or to protect the legal rights, interests, or safety of the website, our users or others. We may also use device identifiers to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, internet service providers or law enforcement agencies in our discretion. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you. 

**Security Measures**  
Our website has reasonable security measures in place to help protect personal information under our control. 

**Why We Use Cookies**  
When you visit some of our sites, we use cookies to keep track of your information. This small piece of program code resides on your computer and stores your contact information for all of our request information sites. We do this so you are not required to re-enter your contact information as you move from one site to another. In addition, some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by us and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. You can generally opt out of the use of cookies by having your browser disable cookies or warn you before accepting a cookie. Look for the cookie options in your browser in the Options or Preferences menu. However, please be aware that some areas of our website may not provide you with an acceptable user experience if you have disabled the use of cookies. 

**Log Files**   
TestDEN web servers retains information about our users through log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Clear GIFs**  
We and our third party advertising companies may employ a software technology called clear GIFs that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to monitor the online movements of users. The main difference between the two is that clear GIFs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear GIFs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information. Clear GIFs can work with existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same site or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited "www.companyA.com", which uses an advertising company's clear GIF, the website or advertising company would match the clear GIF's identifier and the advertising company's cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information would then be given to the advertising company or site. 

**Links From Our Site To Other Sites**  
Some of our sites may contain links to other sites external to our sites. When you access these external websites, the providers of the sites will have access to certain information about you. TestDEN is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any websites which we do not directly control. 

**Contact TestDEN**  
We invite you to contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address: 

TestDEN.com (a division of ACT360 Media Ltd.)  
Suite 1116, 207 W. Hastings St.  
Vancouver, BC  
CANADA V6B 1H7

E-mail us at [comment@testden.com](mailto:comment@testden.com) or call (604) 638-1553.
